Things you should know about me.

I have always found technology massively interesting. My partner is a web designer which sparked my interest with Photoshop initially. I taught myself how to replicate graphics, repair/alter photographs, create fake photos, design logos and banners. All of which was just for fun.

I have now taken a keen interest with the development side of websites, I am currently learning the basics of HTML, CSS, JavaScript plus many more to come, I can honestly say it's becoming my new addition.

Most of my working life so far has been based around providing a great customer experience, but most of all I thrive on working with like minded people bouncing off each other constantly helping one another out, whether that would be for problem solving, self-improvement or improving our working life in general.

Personal Skills

- Loyal and Honest
- Organised
- Dedicated
- Team player
- Improver
- Willingness to learn
- Problem Solver
- Self-motivated
- Positively Pedantic

Contact Details

Name:

Mrs Bree Beale

Address:

10 Chatsworth Road,

Morecambe,

Lancashire

LA4 4JG

Phone:

07713 325 315

Email:

im_breezybree@yahoo.co.uk

Education and Qualification

- 11 GCSE's
- Adobe Photoshop
- Digital Imaging City & Guilds Level 1
- Floristry City & Guilds
 Level 2
- Microsoft Word & Excel

Links to Projects

Git Hub

• <u>imBreezyBree</u>

References

By Request

Employment History

Yorkshire Building Society: October 2014 - Present

Head Cashier / Customer Consultant

- I manage a small team of 4/5 people.
- Good communication between managers local & regional.
- Overseeing all aspects of the day to day running of the Agency.
- Digitalised every aspect of the office e.g. Rota, Holiday Rota, Cash Floats
- Following confidentiality and data protection procedures.

Marsden Building Society / Lancastrian Estates: May 2013 - 2014 Cashier / Lettings Administrator

- Opening / closing of the branch.
- Daily cash / cheque handling & ensuring tills are balanced correctly.
- Offering excellent customer service to the building societies members & handling all enquiries from customers.
- Prediction of cash flow for the week followed by ordering & handling of cash efficiently & accurately.
- Effective time management & be able to prioritise.
- Able to learn / use the Company financial support systems effectively.
- Have good attention to detail & have an honest personality.
- General estate agency administration for both Sales & Lettings departments.

Morris Holbon Ltd (cakes, Cookies & Crafts Shop): April 2009 - April 2013 Customer Service Advisor

- Taking orders via phone, online, email & in person UK & Internationally.
- Adding products & Inputting orders into the operating systems Actinic & Magento.
- Updating product pictures using Photoshop.
- Arranging the dispatch of international orders via a Courier Service, of which I firstly obtained the best service at the lowest price.
- Having a full & good knowledge of all products, therefore being able to advise customers on the products that best suit their needs.
- Creating & updating general forms & logs for the business.
- Completing any task given to me at any time within a suitable timeframe.
- Maintaining a customer rapport to ensure repeat custom.